http://www.bikeparts.com/privacy

Derailleurs
More...
Brake Parts - BMX Gyro
More...
Tires & Tubes
Tires
Tubes
Tube Protection and Repair
More...
Aero Bars, Parts, Levers
More...
Suspension & Dropper Posts
More...
Build Groupos - Drivetrains
Build Kits (bars, stem etc.)
Forks
Forks - Suspension
Forks - Rigid
Fork Maintenance and Service Parts
More...
Rear Shocks
Frame Shocks
Frame Shock Hardware
Frame Shock Service Parts
More...
Pint Glasses, Mugs and Thermos
More...
Pumps and Inflation
Pumps - CO2
Pumps - Frame, Portable
Pumps - Floor
More...
Bags
Bags - Seat, Handlebar, Frame
Bags - Pannier and Trunk
Phone Mounts & Bags
More...
Car Rack Parts -
Bars, Locks, Pads, Etc.
More...
Electronics & Computers
Computers/GPS/HRMs - Bike Mounted
Computers/GPS/HRMs - Wrist-Worn
Computers/GPS/HRMs - Parts, Mounts
More...
DVDs, Books, Maps, Gifts
Books and Maps
Gifts, Goodies and More
Pint Glasses, Mugs and Thermos
More...
Food/Skin Care
Nutrition - Bars, Gel, Drinks
Sunscreen and Skin Care
First Aid & Survival Kits
More...
Water/Hydration
Water Bottles & Containers
Water Bottle Cages
Hydration Packs
More...
Dog Gear
More...
Shorts - Mens Lycra
More...
Shoes
Shoes - Cycling
Shoes - Running and Casual
Shoes - Foot Beds
More...
Triathlete Gear
Hydration - Triathlete/Running/Hiking
Triathlete - Gear, Caps, Goggles
Triathlete - Suits
More...
Brake Fluids
More...
Tire & Tube Maintenance
Tube Protection and Repair
UST/Tubeless Parts
Tire and Tube Tools
More...
Suspension Maintenance
Fork Maintenance and Service Parts
Shock Oil
Frame Shock Service Parts
More...
Component Small Parts
Belt Drive Parts
Cassettes - Lockrings, Spacers, Cogs
Bottom Bracket Parts
More...
Cable and Housing Tools
More...
Multi Tools (folding, portable)
Component Specific Tools
Multi Tools (folding, portable)
Privacy
This is the website of Peak Cycles (Bikeparts.com, Inc.)
1.888.606.1616
Peak Cycles knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our
privacy policy. By visiting Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) Gather?
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com). Here are the types of
information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information,
but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests,
customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we
obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Bikeparts.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously.
Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Bikeparts.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com)
if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary
messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences.
Information from Other Sources: We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when
you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of Peak Cycles' (bikeparts.com) best
features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.
Does Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) Share the Information It Receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only
as described below and with subsidiaries Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com), Inc. controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as
protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal
mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links
(including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to
perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer
information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course,
the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com), Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer
information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with
the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com), our users,
or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however,
this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation
of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity
to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We will never store your entire credit card number.
We only store the last four digits of your credit card number for reference purposes. We do pass the entire credit card number to our
credit card processor during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off (click the log-out button) when
finished using a shared computer.
Children
Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you
may use Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com), your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including
limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Colorado. If you have any concern about privacy at Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com),
please send us a thorough description to contact@Bikeparts.com, and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions,
unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all
information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them
less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Related Practices and Information
Conditions of Use
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example,
you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com); provide information in Your Account; communicate with us by
phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; provide employer information when opening a corporate account; participate in Discussion
Boards or Peak Cycles (bikeparts.com) Chat. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card
information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers).
Automatic Information
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail
address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource
Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; And products you viewed or searched for. During some visits we
may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages,
page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
top
×
Free Shipping Terms and Conditions
Free Shipping (USA orders only)
Free shipping on orders over $75.00.* Oversize items or orders weighing over 50 lbs are not included in this promotion.**
We will choose either FedEx or USPS for your shipping option depending on your location and the weight of your package. Most packages will ship USPS Priority which will arrive in 2-3 days. Heavier items will likely ship FedEx Ground and may be up to a week in some areas.
*International orders do not qualify for free shipping.
*Oversize items may include but are not limited to: framesets, wheelsets, car racks, bikes and storage racks.
Close
×
COVID-19 Update
On behalf of Peak Cycles and BikeParts.com we hope that everyone is safe and well. We will remain open under normal business hours until further notice. We are taking every precaution necessary to remain open.
In our Peak Cycles bike shop in Golden, Colorado we will continue to perform bike repairs and sales. Due to Covid-19 we are not allowing any customers into the shop at this time.
We have a table and bike stands in front of the shop so we can bring products and/or bikes to you outside for purchase. Our service department is also performing pick-up and drop-off of repair bikes outside.
We are not allowing any bike rentals or demos until further notice.
For online customers, BikeParts.com is running at normal capacity as are our shipping companies USPS and Fedex. We have experienced very few delays for most of our US customers over the 2 weeks.
For local online customers, you can pick up your will-call orders at Peak Cycles.
Call ahead for curbside pickup or come to front door and we will grab your order for you.
We are committed to slowing the spread of Covid-19, and to keep our customers, employees, and communities safe. We hope that this horrible situation ends soon and that everyone takes care of themselves both mentally and physically. If you can get out and walk, hike or ride, then take advantage of it. It certainly helps with stress and anxiety during difficult times. Lastly, don't forget to stay in close contact with friends and family, especially those isolated. Thank you for reading and we wish you well.
If you have any questions, please email us at contact@bikeparts.com 24/7 or call 888-606-1616 Mon-Fri 10AM-6PM MST, Sat 10AM-5 PM MST, closed Sun.
Close
